export const bottomFishing = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: '1. Bottom fishing involves the use of a sinker.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      '2. Bottom fishing does not require casting the bait long distances.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: '3. Bottom fishing is effective in still waters.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '4. Bottom fishing requires constant rod movement.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '5. Bottom fishing is often used for catching large fish.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: '6. Bottom fishing requires the use of a float.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '7. Bottom fishing tackle is effective in rivers with a current.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '8. Bottom fishing requires special skills.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: '9. Bottom tackle is used in both freshwater and saltwater.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: '10. Bottom fishing requires constant monitoring of the tackle.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
];
